[Music]
Hello everyone welcome to Indian stock
market So gas today we will talk
Like, comment and share
your love and everyone must
celebrate today Let's take So gas
today we will talk in the big talk section of TalkTools
Subscribe to the channel from Mumbai
Company's fundamentals are quite strong
Company's financial
delivery is ok
General Insurance Company with a target
price of Rs
1550 The
target is a short term delivery you have to
buy
[Music]
Insurance Company
6569 crore
1550 Augmentation strong buy
ok So gas ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company
Financials per
Quarter as on 30 June 2823 The Company
of Rs
4723.62 crore Dr - 13.27% from last
quarter Total Income
546 157 crore and Half 13.84% from last
quarter Total Income of
38 crore Company has reported Net Profit
after tax of 300.36 crore The
Company has private sector aggregate
growth in both motor and healthy health  The
brokerage has given the big
rating ICC Lombard
OK SO Gas Promoters FII Holdings
Promoters hold 48.001%
stock in the company as on 30 June 2023
File Fifth on 22.04% Rates 18.1%
OK SO Gas ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company with target press offer
target is ₹550 Short term delivery you have to buy
Current market price of ICC
Lombard
₹1000
65659 crore Operating financial services
sector
give Namaste Say Radhe Radhe